Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high!
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on!
On your mark!
Camel of other things!
We're on Earth, a legendary!
Hooray!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves!
We run our daunted!
Ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted,
Then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise!
And freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way!
Find one piece!
I'll be the first!
I'll put it be so bad!
Just a good verse!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting!
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave!
In every world I'm feeling alive!
Look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
And here we go!
We go!
You jerk!
You really made me mad, you know that?
This is what you get!
Intimidation!
Megabug!
Come on, it was big enough already!
Am I supposed to be impressed?
Well, you're surprised, right?
I'm a Tiger Blowfish Fish Man!
Scary, huh?
Not really.
I'm kind of curious why you're
talking like that, though.
Then I'll deflate if I keep
my mouth open, you idiot!
The Kraken is still way bigger than you.
Oh, yeah? Fine!
Then how about this?
Don't crush me, damn it! Stop it!
What is zooming?
We're on your side!
You're squashing all of us!
Still a shrimp compared to the Kraken.
If possible!
Well, how's this?
Get up, you fool!
We have come, Your Majesty!
Are you all right down there?
I'm so sorry, my king.
We should have been able to protect
you, and we failed, we pathetic,
worthless vassals!
Never mind that.
More importantly, did
you see the Noah? Yes.
Tragic that it's been moved
under such circumstances.
Curse you, Deccan.
I never thought you would sink so
low as to destroy your own island.
And your own people.
Trust me, your majesty.
We were just as shocked as you were.
We even tried to order an
island-wide evacuation.
But those new fishman pirate bastards
are blocking any transmission.
Even worse, we haven't been able to make
contact with the border guards out at sea.
Prepare to shoot the bubble now!
Hurry!
See?
They won't pick up!
You need to get the king out
of here in some place safe now!
No. Huh?
I'm waiting right here for the princes.
What in blazes?
Someone explain this what's
happening like for starters
where did all these Damn
pirates come from will sir
The Straw Hats are on our side
Jinbei And the princess
Heart Deccan So that's what happened
Alright men Everything is clear to me now
All of you To the plaza Follow
Jinbei Back up the Straw Hats
If the Straw Hats can
handle the more powerful
fighters Our men can suppress
the others It's insane We
tried to arrest them yet
they're fighting To save
our island We should be
ashamed for not trusting them
It's time to make Things right
and give them our support
Great it's Neptune's army Hey no
big deal we can crush them Kill
them all Stand tall and show these
bastards what they're made of
Humble, humble, humble. Hurry up.
March, slave tank.
Turn right and head that way.
Pass.
Worthless klutz.
Just drag the bastard.
Look at that pathetic flesh bag.
That's truly disgusting.
Nico Robin.
Could you perhaps use your
power to free those slaves?
Really?
Are you sure that's wise?
They won't care for fishmen.
I'll knock them unconscious if they
try to take their grudge out on me.
Because the life that they're living
right now, they're even lower than beasts.
This behavior was learned
from the Celestial Dragons.
I won't stand for it.
Count on me.
Thank you.
All our callers! They came off! Hey!
What's the deal here? The hell?
Who's taking the callers
off of the slaves?
What the hell is wrong
with you worthless slaves?
We're free. Was it you?
Why save us when we were
fighting against you?
I can't say no to a handsome man.
In other words, thank Boss Jinbei. Jinbei?
But...
How dare you! They're mine!
Troll net!
Let's put you in chains
What the hell?
This is getting weird.
Cut that out!
Just relax, this won't take long.
Let go.
Hang on, how are there two of you?
Double...
Gee, got Hammond!
We'll do, sir!
Thanks a whole lot for the help, lady.
You bastards treated us like trash.
I'm gonna pay you back for every
beating you gave me and then some.
The enemy just freed all our slaves!
It's a revolt!
This is the border guard
patrol calling, sir.
Have I reached the minister of the left?
Please, you need to
warn the whole kingdom.
It's the Noah, sir.
We've just been informed it's lost power.
As a result, it's begun falling again,
and it's hurling towards the island.
Surely not!
What could this mean?
Where are you calling from?
The air tank, sir.
From the control tower.
That's good.
That means you can warn everyone
about the impending danger.
All our communication centers are down.
But you can help.
You can contact the state-operated
transponder snails all across the country.
Please hurry. Yes, sir.
This is an emergency announcement to
all citizens of the Ryugu Kingdom.
An evacuation has been issued.
The giant ship known as the NOAA
is falling towards Fishman Island.
Everyone must flee the area immediately.
The bubble's gonna break!
The island will be destroyed!
Keep running.
Just forget about your stuff.
We have to leave the island to the sea!
Come on, hurry!
Oh, jeez.
That thing's falling again.
Tim, you better fix
this mess quick, Loopy.
Something must have happened
to Princess Shura Hachi.
What's Tekken trying to pull,
that crazy son of a bitch?
You've got no choice but to run.
That ship will kill us all.
You can leave Heart and
his associates to us.
All of you citizens are
ordered to flee the island.
Now get going!
No way!
Wait, what?
Women and children especially!
Come on, move it!
The Straw Hats may be a
bunch of human pirates,
but they're all down there
fighting to save our island!
We can't just run away and let them
die when they're trying to help us!
He's right.
We asked them to help us and I'm
not going to turn my back on them.
I can't fight with them, but I won't
leave them here to die and run away!
Yes, exactly!
It's the least we can do!
Quiet, all of you!
Listen up!
I'm assigning you a duty.
Tell every other spectator they
need to evacuate right now.
If you're going to stay, then
save the others while you're here.
Is that understood?
I don't have time to
argue with you about it.
So if you want to stay
behind, suit yourself.
All right, outlaws.
Time to face my wrath.
Is this Straw Hat Luffy all right?
It's the Air Tank we've
met once before. Remember?
What is this?
They're broadcasting to the Pirates.
We've heard everything.
We are prepared to take action.
We can see the Noah hurtling
toward the island as we speak.
Oh, Luffy, I don't know what to do.
Do you hear those fools?
They're broadcasting their
conversation across the entire country.
Shirahoshi, straw heart.
I'm afraid that's all we can do.
After we deploy the bubble,
the rest is up to you.
Don't make it more complicated.
Just go for it, okay?
He's still alright.
Thank goodness.
I don't understand what's going on?
What is he doing here?
And more than that, what's
the princess doing with him?
Yeah, the Straw Hat guy's the
one who kidnapped her, right?
He's a human.
And Luffy, everyone
here is counting on you.
Anyone else confused
why the Border Guard's
asking a human pirate to save the island?
Hold on, does this mean that
the human is on board the Noah?
So is he trying to stop it?
Can you hear me?
Straw Hat what prince spook
of ocean he spoke earlier and
It's clear now Heart is keep talking
just tell us what Heart is already
He's not a fish man he's a monster
brought to life by our hatred
The new Fishman Pirates, they're nothing
but remnants of a grudge from ages past.
We allowed their evil to fester
in the shadow of Fishman Island,
and they began to champion
this meaningless grudge.
Flying its flag in some misguided sense
of pride, they fear a future without it.
In truth, they want humans to be evil.
Otherwise, there is no reason
to justify their crusade.
All they desire is bloodshed.
And despite what they say, they
don't want peace for fish man either!
Answer me, dammit!
What did humans do to you
that was so unforgivable?
Why?
What in this world could
inspire such cruelty?
Not one damn thing.
That...
that's your answer?
The simple truth.
We were chosen by heaven
to punish the humans.
That's our purpose.
And we have the power to do so.
I understand now this
sick and pathetic truth.
All of their fury, their hatred, it doesn't
come from experience or logic or fact.
They have no substance.
Just empty cruelty.
Their hatred, it doesn't come
from experience or logic or fact.
They have no substance, just
empty cruelty. So now what?
I get what he's saying, but how
are they going to stop them?
Hey, what are you standing around for?
We've got to get off the island right now!
I can see the shadow of the Nua already!
It's right over our heads!
Hurry, Whip Hachi!
What's happening?
It looks even more
frightening than before.
Humans are worthless.
Evil creatures.
Never forget that, Heart.
They're scum.
Barely fit to serve us.
This is it we're done for ever since the
great pirate era started we've been losing
more and more of our people every day the
humans take the mermaids
to sabo odi and sell
them off some of them went missing this
morning i'm telling you
it's just a matter of
time before fishman island falls filthy
humans we gotta kill
them before they kill us
listen up this man
sacrificed his life to blow
up the human shop and
set the Slave's free!
Tch, sir's right, stupid humans.
Yeah, that guy's awesome.
Sure is.
Yeah, that's what I wanna be.
Count me in.
Have you heard the news?
Arlong sank another human pirate ship!
Now, I'll tell you about those
wretched worms called humans.
Ages ago, when they realized that we,
the fishmen, were the superior race,
they became jealous and afraid.
And then, they began to
persecute our people.
The human race plagued the entire
world like the vermin they are.
They used their numbers to
gain dominance over our people.
Then all of us fishmen were
driven down here to the sea floor.
Listen to me, and don't forget this.
There's this really nice human name
Rayleigh I made friends with on the surface.
And he's not mean like the rest are.
He doesn't even look that
disgusted when he sees me.
Wait, Heart, where are you going?
I don't like your stupid stories, Hachi.
They make me sick.
Humans fear the fishmen.
You must keep the bitterness
of the dead alive, Fruit.
Remember our past.
The very existence of
humanity is pure evil.
You must hate them.
Hate them.
Hate them!
This is terrible!
Tiger's been slain by humans!
The hero of the fishmen is dead! No!
It seems Tiger was not the hero we needed.
Who are you people?
What do you want?
Is it true you gave your blood to humans?
So what if I did?
He was dying, I had to help!
This whole country's mad,
right down to the royal family.
The queen's looking to
make nice with the humans.
How stupid can you be?
Jinbei too.
Heard he joined the
seven warlords recently.
The hour long pirates are the only
ones with any pride these days.
Blatant.
Queen Orohime has been shot!
You see, the humans are evil.
They would even stoop so
low as to kill the queen,
and after she's been so kind to them.
If the royal family is too meek
to hold the humans accountable,
then I can't be loyal
to this kingdom anymore!
I don't want to be ruled
by a bunch of cowards!
The heavens have repaid that
spineless otohime for bowing.
Anyone who wants to forgive humans
deserves a big dose into the head.
I hope you're ready, boys.
It's our time now.
We've been chosen by the heavens,
granted this unstoppable power.
Is that what I think it is?
Those are legendary here.
How did you get your hands on this?
You can duplicate these, can't you?
I'll try.
The people of the Fishman
District must come together.
A proud crusade is about to begin.
No mercy.
We'll kill as many humans as we can.
Until the day we die.
This is our destiny.
We've been chosen by heaven
to bring about the revolution.
The day of reckoning is coming.
This is the end of the
road for all of you.
We've been biding our
time for long enough.
Now we'll take our revenge at last.
We could have stopped all this.
I see now the royal family turned their
eyes away from the fishman district.
In our negligence we allowed it to become
a breeding ground for violence and hatred.
We pretended not to see the resentment that
built up as a result of their isolation.
Even as it descended into lawlessness,
we lived in willful ignorance.
Not so fast.
You going somewhere?
We have to run.
I don't think so.
I thought collecting those
signatures would help,
but I wasn't addressing the true issue.
Please forgive me, Mother.
I'm so sorry.
I know it's difficult,
but you can't pollute the children's
minds with your anger towards humans.
Your resentment.
Do not make it theirs.
But it was too late!
Despite all her pleading, the things she
feared had already been set in motion.
The real enemy was the resentment
brewing inside our hearts.
I felt it too, that hatred.
But refusing to admit that, I looked
outward when I should have looked inward.
My mother's true killer was
the grudge that pestered
among our people while
we turned a blind eye!
And I believe she knew
it in that very moment.
My dear children, it
doesn't matter who hurt me.
Don't become angry.
Please, not on my behalf.
Don't submit to resentment.
Don't let hatred get the better
of you, and my name or any other.
I listened to my mother's words, but part
of me wasn't able to let go of my anger.
I couldn't help but hate
humans for killing her.
Me neither.
A person's pain dies with them.
A grudge is created by the living, and
only the living make it grow stronger.
Because of my prejudice, I overlooked what
was happening in the Fishman district.
And by the time I came to my senses, it
was already spiraling out of control.
If we don't do something soon,
the people of Fishman Island will
be done in by their own hatred.
A foe more deadly than any human.
This will be tough, man.
It's not like the island's bubble.
It might shoot right past the Noah.
It needs to get close
enough to surround it.
No more, no less.
Strawhead, please!
Erase our past!
Set us back to zero!
Eradicate the shadows cast by our
grudge so that we may see the light!
Okay, get ready to fire!
I'm on it!
Here we go!
All we can do is start over.
We must!
Would you give it a rest already?
The rage of our people will never die!
Brother Hachi, just let me
do this my way. Trust me.
Hey, wait a second.
Those guys fighting Horty's
crew in the plaza, aren't they?
Yeah, you're right.
They're the Straw Hat Pirates.
And Boss Jinbei too. What?
That's Foofy's place. You're right.
We did it!
It's in the bubble!
Our minds were made up as
soon as we got to the plaza.
With Jinbei's help, we were
gonna save this island.
Leave it to me and my crew.
That's what friends are for, right?
We should never have
suspected him, human or not.
What's the holdup?
We should go!
Hurry up! Run!
I think I'm gonna stay here. What?
Me too!
Yeah!
Same here!
I am not running away!
Me neither!
Luffy!
There's air on the Noah! Yeah!
That may be!
But I'm going to catch you
along before you get there!
What should we do, Luffy? You'll be okay.
Just follow my lead, and I promise
I won't let Heart hurt you.
Yes, right!
Feeling brave?
Careful, Luffy!
That machine's no match for
the spirit of the squid!
It's a spirit!
That's not spirit!
That's just spit!
Ink.
Fortunately, I can copy
myself with squitting.
The spirit of the squid is under...
No!
I don't want to be dried squid!
Wow!
I didn't know your robot
could shoot fireballs!
How many cool attacks can this baby do?
Wait!
That came out of you?
You really shouldn't have let
your guard down, little guy!
Yeah, like I would.
Wait, Paul!
Be shot!
Be gone!
Who uses their bare hand to stop a hammer?
On second thought, I probably could have
found a less painful way to do that.
Hey, Chopper, I thought that one was
supposed to be your normal-looking form.
Sure you're okay looking so freaky?
I don't care anymore.
I wanted to look human before,
because I didn't have any friends.
But now, I want to be a monster
so I can help Luffy. Gotcha.
I'll slice that smile right off your face!
Bring me the real strongest
swordsman on Fishman Island.
There's no way it's you.
I didn't even break a sweat.
Got you now!
I'm sorry, but your time is over.
Did you hear a word that I said?
I'm gonna save them all!
From you and anything you've got!